Learn Marvelous Designer Tips in 3 Minutes
After a friend's question is saved,
the document cannot be opened again, and various prompt frames are removed.
What is this about?
In fact, there are many reasons for such problems,
mainly related to the system font or the size of the document.
When installing Marvelous Designer,
please make sure that there are no special fonts and non-English words in the installation path.
In other words, please try to avoid using special fonts such as signal, add, etc.,
and avoid Chinese, Japanese, Korean, etc.
In the same way, when storing project files or exporting files,
please ensure that the path and file name are also in line with the above rules.
Paths, such as this computer, local disk, etc. will not be affected.
Just click on the specific path to comply with the previous rules.
Recommend using Arabic, digital, English, and lowercase.
In addition, when using the internal function,
please try to ensure that you read the text,
and that the file path or name is in line with the above rules.
Using special fonts or non-English words is not necessarily a problem,
but avoiding using them can avoid some unnecessary trouble.
In addition, it is sometimes impossible to open the files made in the new version
and open the files made in the new version in the old version.
However, it is possible to open the old version files in the new version software.
In addition, when the entire project file is larger than 2GB,
the files cannot be stored or may be damaged.
The amount of clothing in the video is very small,
only 3mm, and the total number of animated frames is 1,500.
Such project files are likely to be more than 2GB.
When we turn on the display statistics function,
at the bottom left corner of the 3D window,
you can see the number of faces, points, and other data.
Next, let's test to save this file as a project file.
Now go to the folder to check the file storage situation.
When we select this file,
you can see that the size of the entire file has become only more than 200KB,
which means that the storage has failed.
For such animated files that are more than 2GB,
it is best to record and save the project in a separate section at the beginning.
For example, here we recorded about 700 frames,
and then choose to save a project file.
After saving, the number of frames left at the beginning
stays at the last frame recorded just now,
and then delete the animation recorded before.
From the last frame just now,
continue to record the animation.
After recording a new animation,
continue to save as a new project file.
After saving in sections,
you can see that both project files have been successfully saved.
In addition, when the project is more than 2GB,
it can still be translated into Alembic format,
but it is not easy to modify in reverse,
so it is not recommended to directly export.
If you are not sure about the size of the entire project file,
you can first export the ABC file to check it.
The content of this issue ends here.
If you have any questions,
please send a private message or comment.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.